<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Grammar xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
         xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" 
		 xsi:type="AssignmentGrammar">
	<name>Adventure Hooks (Shadowrun)</name>
	<author>Lance Boudreaux</author>
	<description>Generates adventure hooks for Shadowrun.</description>
	<genre>Fantasy</genre>
	<system>Shadowrun</system>
	<category>Encounter</category>
	<parameters />
	<supportsMaxLength>false</supportsMaxLength>
	<items>
		<item name="Start">Take a sample of earth from spiritual lands located deep within an enchanted forest.</item>
		<item name="Start">Search through Indian badlands for the mysterious Running Rain and obtain his secret of weather control.</item>
		<item name="Start">Gather video footage of a Politician's nightly excursions for his election opponent.</item>
		<item name="Start">Eliminate a gang of assassins whose leader claims to be Jesus Christ.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a computer message from one place to another and not tell it's secret when it accidentally goes off.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture a man who has been magically inducing suicide all over the city.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture a professional arsonist before he escapes to another country.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find a way to eliminate a man who has the power to act upon actions before they happen.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop an assassin who is to eliminate a famous conductor during the interlude between music.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect a mars mission rocket from attack by those who wish to steal it.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver an exploding package to the four year old daughter of a corporate official.</item>
		<item name="Start">Shut down the Secret Corner bar which is supposedly an establishment for drug dealers.</item>
		<item name="Start">A runner must locate the creator of an exploding cyber eye and find a way to reverse it's effects. [I'm under the assumption the eye is implanted in the runner looking for it.]</item>
		<item name="Start">Rescue a young girl from the clutches of a psychotic, murderous go gang.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop the infamous Balloon Man before he gives a cyanide filled balloon to another child.</item>
		<item name="Start">Close the gates to a supposed "Highway to Heaven" for a group of Satanists.</item>
		<item name="Start">Travel to a castle inhabited by a Medusa and destroy it.</item>
		<item name="Start">Get revenge upon a small company who sold the wrong group of tough guys land filled with fools gold. </item>
		<item name="Start">Rescue a group of commandos from the forest where they are believed to be held captive.</item>
		<item name="Start">Journey through a nuclear blasted wasteland in search of a radioactive orb.</item>
		<item name="Start">Frighten the hell out of a Yakuza boss and explain that he should not mess with the mob.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture a man who kills only by the light of a full moon.</item>
		<item name="Start">Defeat the Orange Crush battle brawl team in a tournament.</item>
		<item name="Start">Destroy a corporate warehouse at exactly ten past eight p.m.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal a large gold stone from an Indian cave and keep half the profits.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop the onslaught of a Satanic group who believe they cannot be killed.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a group of 50 squatters from food rioting without killing a single one.</item>
		<item name="Start">Rig an entire playground with boobytraps designed to eliminate children.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a bomb from detonating inside a crowded shopping mall.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect a small town from the creatures which have crossed through a hole in space.</item>
		<item name="Start">Wait along a rural road and ambush a group of illegal traders as they walk by.</item>
		<item name="Start">Transport a man with a horrible transformation disease to a major hospital.</item>
		<item name="Start">Investigate activity at a go gang headquarters unknowing they are about to attack in mass.</item>
		<item name="Start">When an EMP knocks out cyber eyes on a investigative run what will the runners do?</item>
		<item name="Start">Travel to the location where a mysterious spacecraft has crashed.</item>
		<item name="Start">Rescue a group of prisoners from a maximum security prison.</item>
		<item name="Start">Destroy a small nuclear generator which produces a mysterious blue radioactive haze.</item>
		<item name="Start">During a homecoming dance, assassinate a Politician's daughter.</item>
		<item name="Start">A powerful, but primitive, group of Indians is about to attack. Stop them.</item>
		<item name="Start">Eliminate the creature which haunt a very old house.</item>
		<item name="Start">Someone is watching the residents of a town block and want whoever is doing it brought to the police.</item>
		<item name="Start">A powerful magical psychotic is about to go absolutely nuts but must be transported to an institution.</item>
		<item name="Start">When a group of environmentalists lose their land to developers they do not give up easy.</item>
		<item name="Start">A man says he has the power to turn the world into pure evil.  The runners know where he is.</item>
		<item name="Start">A group of rebellious trolls is about to mount an attack.  Eliminate some of the group so it is not possible.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture an AWOL soldier who fled into the countryside with an appaloosa.</item>
		<item name="Start">One man offers to pay a runner for an old fashion, western gunfight. [I personally liked this one.]</item>
		<item name="Start">Extract a bride and groom during their wedding ceremony.</item>
		<item name="Start">Keep a messenger from traveling from Los Angeles to Seattle.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a go gang which has been menacing the streets using heavy weaponry.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect a crew reconstructing a destroyed oil pump from attacking environmental radicals.</item>
		<item name="Start">Swipe a prototype microchip recently stolen by a group known as the Tech Masters.</item>
		<item name="Start">When a woman falls victim to a magical sadness disease, the quickened spell must be eliminated.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find out why rain clouds keep coming from the same valley in the mountains.</item>
		<item name="Start">Break through shielding of a conference room and record the conversation which is taking place on the inside.</item>
		<item name="Start">56. Season's Greetings: Find out who keeps putting explosives in children's Christmas toys.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect the underground silo of an experimental hyper space rocket from incursions.</item>
		<item name="Start">Race against a woman and document her cheating.</item>
		<item name="Start">Screw up the plans of a group of missionaries to build a bridge for a village.</item>
		<item name="Start">When the half moon rises a call is made by a man terrified by the creature the moon had brought.</item>
		<item name="Start">Transport weapons through an area known as hijacker's haven.</item>
		<item name="Start">Intelligence reports a surge of weapons into a bad neighborhood.  Get video proof.</item>
		<item name="Start">Go into a compound after a group of other runners and try to stop them before they enter a trap.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a mage who has a spell which easily ignites metals.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal a vial of magical stardust from a magical research facility.</item>
		<item name="Start">Get a band of bikers to leave town without killing them.</item>
		<item name="Start">Rescue a man from a time loop from within a corporate facility.</item>
		<item name="Start">Show a wannabe shadowrunner the ropes and make sure he gets killed by an enemy.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a captured man into a chamber within corporate grounds.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kidnap a simsense star and deliver her to a deranged man.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a group of vampires who use a neighborhood as their killing grounds.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kill a cop who uses mind games on other cops to get his way.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a gang war anyway possible before it erupts into full scale war.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a man into the desert and help him find his lost soul.</item>
		<item name="Start">Journey to the castle of the damned and bring back scales from a black dragon.</item>
		<item name="Start">When a 747 crashes the runners must steal a shipment of drugs from within the wreckage.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect a town when it is invaded by a warring tribe.</item>
		<item name="Start">Journey to an ancient lost city and bring back proof of it existence.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find and retrieve a young soldier who is AWOL, hiding in the woods.</item>
		<item name="Start">When a boat sinks, rescue the political survivors before the people who bombed them have a chance to return.</item>
		<item name="Start">Assassinate a well known simsense star during the grand finale of her performance.</item>
		<item name="Start">Convince a factory owner that he should hire a special worker.</item>
		<item name="Start">A news hero is found to be fake.  Capture the media man who set up the fake.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a eulogy to the site of a very important funeral.</item>
		<item name="Start">Journey to the bottom of a pit to retrieve a scientist's dropped instrument.</item>
		<item name="Start">Enforce a fee that must be paid by all before traveling through a secret passage.</item>
		<item name="Start">Penetrate a makeshift fortress set up by a group of psycho kids and administer a drug to them.</item>
		<item name="Start">Destroy a creature which is causing a giant sand storm.</item>
		<item name="Start">Cut a man in two so the evil and good spirits within him way separate.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a drug into the depths of a riot area to stop a horrid change to a person.</item>
		<item name="Start">Eliminate the lights surrounding an amusement park which bother neighbors.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find out why everyone suddenly disappeared from a town.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a man into a snowy region and leave him for dead.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kidnap a group of babies who all have the same birth date.</item>
		<item name="Start">Take on an additional runner for a single shadowrun.</item>
		<item name="Start">When a radio prank develops fears of an apocalypse, the runners must protect a street from looters.</item>
		<item name="Start">A rare disease is mutating normal felines into horrible creatures. Protect residents from them.</item>
		<item name="Start">Restart an old electric generator which has been taken over by gang members.</item>
		<item name="Start">Travel a hundred miles across an ice ridge to rescue a corporate official.</item>
		<item name="Start">When a murderous free spirit roams, the only sign is its nonexistent shadow.</item>
		<item name="Start">The runners are hired by the UCAS military to go and stop a band of AWOL men marauding the local countryside.</item>
		<item name="Start">The runners are hired to kill a band of people who they say are AWOL and who they say are marauding the local countryside. The truth is that one man is a scientist who does not want the designs for a powerful laser weapon to get out.</item>
		<item name="Start">The runners are hired to infiltrate a restaurant call Thieves World and to locate the kingpin and bring him to their employer.</item>
		<item name="Start">Hired to follow a person through the ultimate gate of astral space. The one which supposedly leads to everyone's past life and report all he finds out.</item>
		<item name="Start">Hired to assassinate an old lady in a nursing home.</item>
		<item name="Start">Hired to patrol a length of trail where eagle poachers have been shooting from.</item>
		<item name="Start">107. Jackson's Valley: Track down a person in a small town who keeps attempting to destroy the dam which keeps a river from destroying the town.</item>
		<item name="Start">Fight the queen of the Urban Combat Zone and kill her.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kill the oldest man on earth for the second oldest man on earth.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kill a killer which knocks on doors and kills people.</item>
		<item name="Start">Rid a house of free demon spirits.</item>
		<item name="Start">Shut down a privet lab which does hideous experiments on animals.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kill your childhood friend who is a free lance assassin.</item>
		<item name="Start">Destroy a company which dumps toxic waste for a living.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal the prototype for a laser eye from a large company.</item>
		<item name="Start">Bring in human sacrifices for a satanic cult.</item>
		<item name="Start">Destroy the Hunter drones wired with explosives before he releases them upon the town.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture the old man who has been living in the castle for over 100 years.</item>
		<item name="Start">Play the moder version of Russian roulette.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture the man of eyes who has been selling eyes filled with explosives to the public.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture the shape changing griffin before he kills anyone else.</item>
		<item name="Start">Hired to find the only men capable of defeating the ultimate Battletech champion who has not been seen for five years.</item>
		<item name="Start">Destroy the organization of masochists called Second Earth who wish to refine" the planet for the purely violent.</item>
		<item name="Start">A college fraternity wishes to get back at another for a prank.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal the research of a man who wishes to combine Magic and The Matrix in a way that would allow immortality.</item>
		<item name="Start">Travel to the Datalas space station to stop people who have taken it over and used a radar dish to "turn up the heat" on Seattle.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find and rescue the survivor of an old secret crashed U.S. space probe before any other corps get to him.</item>
		<item name="Start">Destroy a fully automatic rail gun aimed at Seattle.</item>
		<item name="Start">Close down a simsense facility which brainwashes its customers.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal the design for a Mag 5 eye through the matrix.</item>
		<item name="Start">"Convince" a night club owner that it would be a good idea to hire a rich guy's daughter.</item>
		<item name="Start">Go through the gate to where magic is the norm and you must be special to go into regular space.</item>
		<item name="Start">Go to the front lines of a real gang war.</item>
		<item name="Start">Peacefully convince two gangs that it is not a good idea to kill each other.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal the amulet from someone's privet collection that signifies that your employer is the right king.</item>
		<item name="Start">Purposely lead a group of men into an ambush.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal a stash of solid gold German Iron Crosses which habe been added to a museum collection.</item>
		<item name="Start">Lead a seppuku ceremony and be the be header.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture a runaway science experiment which is a large mutated man.</item>
		<item name="Start">Get rid of the government of trolls which have taken over a small town and made themselves gods.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find the ancient elders who know all to find the cure to the employer's daughter's disease.</item>
		<item name="Start">Search the jungle for an underground lost city and bring back information on its location and content.</item>
		<item name="Start">Bring down a renegade in a tank in the desert.</item>
		<item name="Start">Track down someone who starts fires using plastics and a remote control.</item>
		<item name="Start">Lead an air strike on a corporate chemical weapons facility.</item>
		<item name="Start">Fight with one gang to eliminate the other.</item>
		<item name="Start">Burn down the hotel inhabited by demons.</item>
		<item name="Start">Raid the religious town of St. Nazaire and capture the sacred skull which they worship.</item>
		<item name="Start">Save the hostages taken prisoner at a casino by an Ex-Military mad man.</item>
		<item name="Start">Quietly snipe off a leading politician.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect a religious group as they trek deep into Quebec looking for a mystical new world.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a rich guy's son who is on his way to Dee-Cee determined to rid the city of crime by himself.</item>
		<item name="Start">Bring back a vile of life from the mystical Circus Maximus which roams the desert.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal a lot of money from a rich guy's vault.</item>
		<item name="Start">Transport a load of financial certificates from one place to another.</item>
		<item name="Start">Track a decker name Twixt and capture him for a company he stole millions for.</item>
		<item name="Start">Race a bike in the road race for a company.</item>
		<item name="Start">Obtain the plans to mechnoid robots and fight some too.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kill the man who has been bringing flood weather to many farms.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal a truck load of ancient Egyptian stuff from a museum.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect a group lost in time as they make their way back to a portal in exchange for technology.</item>
		<item name="Start">Bodyguard a star for several nights.</item>
		<item name="Start">Help a tribesman become the leader of his tribe and then assassinate him so he'll look like a martyr.</item>
		<item name="Start">Follow a man's out of body body into astral space and defeat the evil force which is giving him nightmares.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop an arsonist from burning down his girlfriends house.</item>
		<item name="Start">Help orks get rid of some trolls who have taken over part of the underground.</item>
		<item name="Start">Assassinate the leaders of an elven religious group in Tir Tangire.</item>
		<item name="Start">Get a pendent out of a vault of treasures.</item>
		<item name="Start">169. Force Eagle's War: Destroy the AWOL Force Eagle air wing.</item>
		<item name="Start">Assassinate one family so that the other will be able to have the house.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture the member of a night watch program who is using the protection to rob and kill people.</item>
		<item name="Start">Beat the hell out of a biker because he won't pay his bar tab.</item>
		<item name="Start">Take a magical sculpture from an ancient city in Azlan.</item>
		<item name="Start">Assassinate the leader of small city state which has started in the Ozarks.</item>
		<item name="Start">Assist a criminal's escape from prison.</item>
		<item name="Start">Make a weapons deal with an illegal company and transport the shipment.</item>
		<item name="Start">Help fight a fire raging through the forest.</item>
		<item name="Start">Get a refund from a magician who is selling shoddy magical goods.</item>
		<item name="Start">Get a picture of the leader of one of the largest cults.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect an orks beer wagon from marauders.</item>
		<item name="Start">Teach a group of wanna-bees to be real shadowrunners.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver the design for a new type of assault rifle to him.</item>
		<item name="Start">Steal the design to one of the strangest toys ever made.</item>
		<item name="Start">Go on a world wide assassination assignment.</item>
		<item name="Start">Destroy the raiders of a small country side village.</item>
		<item name="Start">Follow a group of cops and get evidence of their wrong doings.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find out why there is a voice emanating from a brick wall in a basement.</item>
		<item name="Start">A real atlas mech is built and must be destroyed before its creator uses it to destroy someone.</item>
		<item name="Start">Rescue the Sonics star player before he is killed by his captors.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find out why a decker is tormented every time he connects to his deck.</item>
		<item name="Start">Receive a challenge from a defeated enemy.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find them and get the spell formula for immortality.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a terrible creature formed on the mages day of warship.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find the queen of a colony of rock worms and kill it.</item>
		<item name="Start">Join the group and bring back a membership certificate.</item>
		<item name="Start">Exorcise an evil spirit from a young woman.</item>
		<item name="Start">Fight a Predator colony on your terms.</item>
		<item name="Start">Enter a pyramid and bring back the solid gold skull of an ancient mummy.</item>
		<item name="Start">Journey to a region called The Claw and bring back information on their culture.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a project that would mean the end to all magic.</item>
		<item name="Start">Sabotage the boat of the client's opponent's racing team.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop an important business man, who has gone psycho, without harming him.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver drugs to rose cafe and then screw them out of their money.</item>
		<item name="Start">Break an important person out of a minimum security prison.</item>
		<item name="Start">Search the city for individuals who are willing to become the host bodies for an insect shaman cult.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a group of pranksters who's tricks are beginning to turn lethal.</item>
		<item name="Start">Travel into the forest to a magical mine which holds a stash of powerful, and evil black gold.</item>
		<item name="Start">Track down the person who has embedded an organic/mechanical creature into your client.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a sasquatch back to his home, which has been taken over by human bigots.</item>
		<item name="Start">Travel into a warehouse under siege and provide support for as long as it takes.</item>
		<item name="Start">Blow up an entire city block for the New World terrorist group.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a train which is rapidly heading towards a downed bridge.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kidnap anybody and deliver that person to a man who's ego is so bad it demands he have a slave.</item>
		<item name="Start">Safely deliver a peaceful shaman across the countryside without using vehicles, electronics, or violence.</item>
		<item name="Start">Track down a group of children who have been missing for more then 2 years.</item>
		<item name="Start">216. 99%: Take the last percentage of a crystal needed by a company from an armed magical group.</item>
		<item name="Start">Transport a man who is prone to horrible bad luck, over a far distance.</item>
		<item name="Start">Fix a one on one brawl so your client wins, without the opponent knowing you helped.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kidnap a corporate official's child from his home and hold it for ransom.</item>
		<item name="Start">Get rid of an ice creature which has been inhabiting a store owner's freezer.</item>
		<item name="Start">Take the remaining money from a vault in a ghost town.</item>
		<item name="Start">Assassinate the king of an Indian tribe for your client.</item>
		<item name="Start">Snap a guy back into reality by using whatever means necessary.</item>
		<item name="Start">Get aboard a ghost train which occasionally shows up at a city stop.</item>
		<item name="Start">Attempt to assassinate a man who always manages to avoid the shot.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find the past of a young amnesic and report it to the police.</item>
		<item name="Start">Eliminate a 99 year old man who continues to run a large crime ring.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a woman before she hangs herself for an ex boyfriend.</item>
		<item name="Start">Administer a nightmare drug to a high level politician.</item>
		<item name="Start">Eliminate a pirate who constantly harasses shipping on land, sea and air.</item>
		<item name="Start">A man who thinks he's the riddler keep pranking the city. Stop him.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a shipment of poisoned balloons from reaching an orphanage.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find out who is poisoning children through the use of candy.</item>
		<item name="Start">Fire off a group of well guarded cannons on a naval base.</item>
		<item name="Start">Stop a magical onslaught which has the power to turn cities into dust.</item>
		<item name="Start">Rescue a woman who is about to be executed by guillotine.</item>
		<item name="Start">Travel to a place where a crevasse has opened up revealing an apparently bottomless pit and find the bottom.</item>
		<item name="Start">Place a hypnotic toy into a baby nursery so the children will go nuts.</item>
		<item name="Start">Crash a drug party and eliminate the people who put it on.</item>
		<item name="Start">Find an innocent looking dog which is really the good form of an evil shape shifter.</item>
		<item name="Start">Inject a man and his girlfriend with a drug that instantly freezes their bodies.</item>
		<item name="Start">Calm a squatter camp before they decide to riot in the city.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a magical, and wanted, umbrella focus to its owner.</item>
		<item name="Start">Take out a high tech catapult which threatens the city and capture its creator.</item>
		<item name="Start">Deliver a load of laughing gas into the city council's center chambers.</item>
		<item name="Start">Kill a dissatisfied workers slave driving and mean boss.</item>
		<item name="Start">Capture a moral less killer who is responsible for the deaths of many people.</item>
		<item name="Start">Screw up a mage's hermantic circle before he has a chance to summon a powerful demon.</item>
		<item name="Start">Eliminate the gang which threatens a walkway in the city.</item>
		<item name="Start">Protect a group of religious people as they make a dangerous pilgrimage for their god.</item>
	</items>
</Grammar>